{
  "name": "Basic Arithmetic",
  "description": "Test your knowledge of addition, subtraction, multiplication, and division.",
  "questions": [
    {
      "prompt": "What does 1 + 1 equal?",
      "options": [
        "1",
        "0",
        "2",
        "-1"
      ],
      "answer": "2"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "6 / 2 =",
      "options": [
        "0",
        "1",
        "4",
        "3"
      ],
      "answer": "3"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "What is the result when you subtract 2 from 7?",
      "options": [
        "3",
        "5",
        "-5",
        "9"
      ],
      "answer": "5"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "What is 6 x 4?",
      "options": [
        "24",
        "2",
        "6",
        "22"
      ],
      "answer": "24"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Name the operation used here: 4 + 3 = 7.",
      "options": [
        "Subtraction",
        "Multiplication",
        "Division",
        "Addition"
      ],
      "answer": "Addition"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "8 / 1 =",
      "options": [
        "1",
        "8",
        "81",
        "7"
      ],
      "answer": "8"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "10 + 3 + 2 =",
      "options": [
        "15",
        "9",
        "13",
        "12"
      ],
      "answer": "15"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "5 x 5 =",
      "options": [
        "5",
        "25",
        "0",
        "55"
      ],
      "answer": "25"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "What does 11 - 4 + 1 equal?",
      "options": [
        "5",
        "16",
        "7",
        "8"
      ],
      "answer": "8"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Name the operation used here: 10 - 1 = 9.",
      "options": [
        "Multiplication",
        "Subtraction",
        "Division",
        "Addition"
      ],
      "answer": "Subtraction"
    }
  ],
  "scores": []
}
